[
  {
    "question": "A welder received an order to make a 1 million liter cube-shaped tank. If he has only 4x2 meter sheets of metal that can be cut, how many metal sheets will be required for this order? (1 cubic meter = 1,000 liters)",
    "choices": [
      "92",
      "90",
      "82",
      "78",
      "75"
    ],
    "answer": "E",
    "link": "https://gmatclub.com/forum/a-welder-received-an-order-to-make-a-1-million-liter-126154.html"
  },
  {
    "question": "A train traveling at a constant speed down a straight track crosses a certain line on the track. If the rear wheels of the train cross the line 2 seconds after the front wheels, and the centers of the rear and front wheels are 100 feet apart, which of the following expresses the speed of the train in miles per hour?<br>1 mile = 5280 feet",
    "choices": [
      "<span class=MathJax_Preview style=color:inherit><span class=MJXp-math id=MJXp-Span-1><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-2 style=margin-left:0em;margin-right:0em>(</span><span class=MJXp-mn id=MJXp-Span-3>100</span><span class=MJXp-mrow id=MJXp-Span-4><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-5 style=margin-left:0.111em;margin-right:0.111em>/</span></span><span class=MJXp-mn id=MJXp-Span-6>5280</span><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-7 style=margin-left:0em;margin-right:0em>)</span><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-8 style=margin-left:0em;margin-right:0em>(</span><span class=MJXp-msubsup id=MJXp-Span-9><span class=MJXp-mn id=MJXp-Span-10 style=margin-right:0.05em>60</span><span class=\"MJXp-mn MJXp-script\" id=MJXp-Span-11 style=vertical-align:0.5em>2</span></span><span class=MJXp-mrow id=MJXp-Span-12><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-13 style=margin-left:0.111em;margin-right:0.111em>/</span></span><span class=MJXp-mn id=MJXp-Span-14>2</span><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-15 style=margin-left:0em;margin-right:0em>)</span></span></span><span class=\"MathJax MathJax_Processed sf-hidden\" id=MathJax-Element-1-Frame tabindex=0></span>",
      "<span class=MathJax_Preview style=color:inherit><span class=MJXp-math id=MJXp-Span-16><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-17 style=margin-left:0em;margin-right:0em>(</span><span class=MJXp-mn id=MJXp-Span-18>100</span><span class=MJXp-mrow id=MJXp-Span-19><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-20 style=margin-left:0.111em;margin-right:0.111em>/</span></span><span class=MJXp-mn id=MJXp-Span-21>5280</span><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-22 style=margin-left:0em;margin-right:0em>)</span><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-23 style=margin-left:0em;margin-right:0em>(</span><span class=MJXp-mn id=MJXp-Span-24>60</span><span class=MJXp-mrow id=MJXp-Span-25><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-26 style=margin-left:0.111em;margin-right:0.111em>/</span></span><span class=MJXp-mn id=MJXp-Span-27>2</span><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-28 style=margin-left:0em;margin-right:0em>)</span></span></span><span class=\"MathJax MathJax_Processed sf-hidden\" id=MathJax-Element-2-Frame tabindex=0></span>",
      "<span class=MathJax_Preview style=color:inherit><span class=MJXp-math id=MJXp-Span-29><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-30 style=margin-left:0em;margin-right:0em>(</span><span class=MJXp-mn id=MJXp-Span-31>100</span><span class=MJXp-mrow id=MJXp-Span-32><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-33 style=margin-left:0.111em;margin-right:0.111em>/</span></span><span class=MJXp-mn id=MJXp-Span-34>5280</span><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-35 style=margin-left:0em;margin-right:0em>)</span><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-36 style=margin-left:0em;margin-right:0em>(</span><span class=MJXp-mn id=MJXp-Span-37>2</span><span class=MJXp-mrow id=MJXp-Span-38><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-39 style=margin-left:0.111em;margin-right:0.111em>/</span></span><span class=MJXp-msubsup id=MJXp-Span-40><span class=MJXp-mn id=MJXp-Span-41 style=margin-right:0.05em>60</span><span class=\"MJXp-mn MJXp-script\" id=MJXp-Span-42 style=vertical-align:0.5em>2</span></span><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-43 style=margin-left:0em;margin-right:0em>)</span></span></span><span class=\"MathJax MathJax_Processed sf-hidden\" id=MathJax-Element-3-Frame tabindex=0></span>",
      "<span class=MathJax_Preview style=color:inherit><span class=MJXp-math id=MJXp-Span-44><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-45 style=margin-left:0em;margin-right:0em>(</span><span class=MJXp-mn id=MJXp-Span-46>100</span><span class=MJXp-mrow id=MJXp-Span-47><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-48 style=margin-left:0.111em;margin-right:0.111em>/</span></span><span class=MJXp-msubsup id=MJXp-Span-49><span class=MJXp-mn id=MJXp-Span-50 style=margin-right:0.05em>60</span><span class=\"MJXp-mn MJXp-script\" id=MJXp-Span-51 style=vertical-align:0.5em>2</span></span><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-52 style=margin-left:0em;margin-right:0em>)</span><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-53 style=margin-left:0em;margin-right:0em>(</span><span class=MJXp-mn id=MJXp-Span-54>5280</span><span class=MJXp-mrow id=MJXp-Span-55><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-56 style=margin-left:0.111em;margin-right:0.111em>/</span></span><span class=MJXp-mn id=MJXp-Span-57>2</span><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-58 style=margin-left:0em;margin-right:0em>)</span></span></span><span class=\"MathJax MathJax_Processing sf-hidden\" id=MathJax-Element-4-Frame tabindex=0></span>",
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "link": "https://gmatclub.com/forum/a-train-traveling-at-a-constant-speed-down-a-straight-track-87124.html"
  },
  {
    "question": "If an automobile averaged 22.5 miles per gallon of gasoline, approximately how many kilometers per liter of gasoline did the automobile average? (1 mile = 1.6 kilometers and 1 gallon = 3.8 liters, both rounded to the nearest tenth.)",
    "choices": [
      "3.7",
      "9.5",
      "31.4",
      "53.4",
      "136.8"
    ],
    "answer": "B",
    "link": "https://gmatclub.com/forum/if-an-automobile-averaged-22-5-miles-per-gallon-of-gasoline-109083.html"
  },
  {
    "error": "7_25_47 PM.html",
    "message": "cannot unpack non-iterable NoneType object"
  },
  {
    "question": "<a href=http://gmatclub.com/forum/quantitative-review-2nd-edition-directory-164896.html class=postlink><span style=color:#459926><span style=font-weight:bold>The Official Guide For GMAT\u00ae Quantitative Review, 2ND Edition</span></span></a><br><br>Temperatures in degrees Celsius (C) can be converted to temperatures in degrees Fahrenheit (F) by the formula <span class=MathJax_Preview style=color:inherit><span class=MJXp-math id=MJXp-Span-1><span class=\"MJXp-mi MJXp-italic\" id=MJXp-Span-2>F</span><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-3 style=margin-left:0.333em;margin-right:0.333em>=</span><span class=MJXp-mfrac id=MJXp-Span-4 style=vertical-align:0.25em><span class=\"MJXp-box MJXp-script\"><span class=MJXp-mn id=MJXp-Span-5>9</span></span><span class=MJXp-box style=margin-top:-0.9em><span class=MJXp-denom><span><span class=MJXp-rule style=\"height:1em;border-top:none;border-bottom:1px solid;margin:0.1em 0px\"></span></span><span><span class=\"MJXp-box MJXp-script\"><span class=MJXp-mn id=MJXp-Span-6>5</span></span></span></span></span></span><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-7 style=margin-left:0.267em;margin-right:0.267em>\u2217</span><span class=\"MJXp-mi MJXp-italic\" id=MJXp-Span-8>C</span><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-9 style=margin-left:0.267em;margin-right:0.267em>+</span><span class=MJXp-mn id=MJXp-Span-10>32</span></span></span><span class=\"MathJax MathJax_Processed sf-hidden\" id=MathJax-Element-1-Frame tabindex=0></span>. What is the temperature at which F = C?",
    "choices": [
      "20\u00b0",
      "(32/5)\u00b0",
      "0\u00b0",
      "-20\u00b0",
      "-40\u00b0"
    ],
    "answer": "E",
    "link": "http://gmatclub.com/forum/quantitative-review-2nd-edition-directory-164896.html class=postlink"
  },
  {
    "question": "The rear wheels of a car crossed a certain line 0.5 second after the front wheels crossed the same line. If the centers of the front and rear wheels are 20 feet apart and the car traveled in a straight line at a constant speed, which of the following gives the speed of the car in miles per hour? (5280 feet = 1 mile)",
    "choices": [
      "<span class=MathJax_Preview style=color:inherit><span class=MJXp-math id=MJXp-Span-1><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-2 style=margin-left:0em;margin-right:0em>(</span><span class=MJXp-mfrac id=MJXp-Span-3 style=vertical-align:0.25em><span class=\"MJXp-box MJXp-script\"><span class=MJXp-mn id=MJXp-Span-4>20</span></span><span class=MJXp-box style=margin-top:-0.9em><span class=MJXp-denom><span><span class=MJXp-rule style=\"height:1em;border-top:none;border-bottom:1px solid;margin:0.1em 0px\"></span></span><span><span class=\"MJXp-box MJXp-script\"><span class=MJXp-mn id=MJXp-Span-5>5280</span></span></span></span></span></span><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-6 style=margin-left:0em;margin-right:0em>)</span><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-7 style=margin-left:0em;margin-right:0em>(</span><span class=MJXp-mfrac id=MJXp-Span-8 style=vertical-align:0.25em><span class=\"MJXp-box MJXp-script\"><span class=MJXp-msubsup id=MJXp-Span-9><span class=MJXp-mn id=MJXp-Span-10 style=margin-right:0.05em>60</span><span class=\"MJXp-mn MJXp-script\" id=MJXp-Span-11 style=vertical-align:0.5em>2</span></span></span><span class=MJXp-box style=margin-top:-0.9em><span class=MJXp-denom><span><span class=MJXp-rule style=\"height:1em;border-top:none;border-bottom:1px solid;margin:0.1em 0px\"></span></span><span><span class=\"MJXp-box MJXp-script\"><span class=MJXp-mn id=MJXp-Span-12>0.5</span></span></span></span></span></span><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-13 style=margin-left:0em;margin-right:0em>)</span></span></span><span class=\"MathJax MathJax_Processed sf-hidden\" id=MathJax-Element-1-Frame tabindex=0></span><br>",
      "<span class=MathJax_Preview style=color:inherit><span class=MJXp-math id=MJXp-Span-14><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-15 style=margin-left:0em;margin-right:0em>(</span><span class=MJXp-mfrac id=MJXp-Span-16 style=vertical-align:0.25em><span class=\"MJXp-box MJXp-script\"><span class=MJXp-mn id=MJXp-Span-17>20</span></span><span class=MJXp-box style=margin-top:-0.9em><span class=MJXp-denom><span><span class=MJXp-rule style=\"height:1em;border-top:none;border-bottom:1px solid;margin:0.1em 0px\"></span></span><span><span class=\"MJXp-box MJXp-script\"><span class=MJXp-mn id=MJXp-Span-18>5280</span></span></span></span></span></span><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-19 style=margin-left:0em;margin-right:0em>)</span><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-20 style=margin-left:0em;margin-right:0em>(</span><span class=MJXp-mfrac id=MJXp-Span-21 style=vertical-align:0.25em><span class=\"MJXp-box MJXp-script\"><span class=MJXp-mn id=MJXp-Span-22>60</span></span><span class=MJXp-box style=margin-top:-0.9em><span class=MJXp-denom><span><span class=MJXp-rule style=\"height:1em;border-top:none;border-bottom:1px solid;margin:0.1em 0px\"></span></span><span><span class=\"MJXp-box MJXp-script\"><span class=MJXp-mn id=MJXp-Span-23>0.5</span></span></span></span></span></span><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-24 style=margin-left:0em;margin-right:0em>)</span></span></span><span class=\"MathJax MathJax_Processed sf-hidden\" id=MathJax-Element-2-Frame tabindex=0></span><br>",
      "<span class=MathJax_Preview style=color:inherit><span class=MJXp-math id=MJXp-Span-25><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-26 style=margin-left:0em;margin-right:0em>(</span><span class=MJXp-mfrac id=MJXp-Span-27 style=vertical-align:0.25em><span class=\"MJXp-box MJXp-script\"><span class=MJXp-mn id=MJXp-Span-28>20</span></span><span class=MJXp-box style=margin-top:-0.9em><span class=MJXp-denom><span><span class=MJXp-rule style=\"height:1em;border-top:none;border-bottom:1px solid;margin:0.1em 0px\"></span></span><span><span class=\"MJXp-box MJXp-script\"><span class=MJXp-mn id=MJXp-Span-29>5280</span></span></span></span></span></span><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-30 style=margin-left:0em;margin-right:0em>)</span><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-31 style=margin-left:0em;margin-right:0em>(</span><span class=MJXp-mfrac id=MJXp-Span-32 style=vertical-align:0.25em><span class=\"MJXp-box MJXp-script\"><span class=MJXp-mn id=MJXp-Span-33>0.5</span></span><span class=MJXp-box style=margin-top:-0.9em><span class=MJXp-denom><span><span class=MJXp-rule style=\"height:1em;border-top:none;border-bottom:1px solid;margin:0.1em 0px\"></span></span><span><span class=\"MJXp-box MJXp-script\"><span class=MJXp-msubsup id=MJXp-Span-34><span class=MJXp-mn id=MJXp-Span-35 style=margin-right:0.05em>60</span><span class=\"MJXp-mn MJXp-script\" id=MJXp-Span-36 style=vertical-align:0.5em>2</span></span></span></span></span></span></span><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-37 style=margin-left:0em;margin-right:0em>)</span></span></span><span class=\"MathJax MathJax_Processed sf-hidden\" id=MathJax-Element-3-Frame tabindex=0></span><br>",
      "<span class=MathJax_Preview style=color:inherit><span class=MJXp-math id=MJXp-Span-38><span class=MJXp-mfrac id=MJXp-Span-39 style=vertical-align:0.25em><span class=\"MJXp-box MJXp-script\"><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-40>(</span><span class=MJXp-mn id=MJXp-Span-41>20</span><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-42>)</span><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-43>(</span><span class=MJXp-mn id=MJXp-Span-44>5280</span><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-45>)</span></span><span class=MJXp-box style=margin-top:-0.9em><span class=MJXp-denom><span><span class=MJXp-rule style=\"height:1em;border-top:none;border-bottom:1px solid;margin:0.1em 0px\"></span></span><span><span class=\"MJXp-box MJXp-script\"><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-46>(</span><span class=MJXp-msubsup id=MJXp-Span-47><span class=MJXp-mn id=MJXp-Span-48 style=margin-right:0.05em>60</span><span class=\"MJXp-mn MJXp-script\" id=MJXp-Span-49 style=vertical-align:0.5em>2</span></span><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-50>)</span><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-51>(</span><span class=MJXp-mn id=MJXp-Span-52>0.5</span><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-53>)</span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span><span class=\"MathJax MathJax_Processing sf-hidden\" id=MathJax-Element-4-Frame tabindex=0></span><br>",
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "link": "https://gmatclub.com/forum/the-rear-wheels-of-a-car-crossed-a-certain-line-0-5-second-135753.html"
  },
  {
    "question": "If an object travels 100 feet in 2 seconds, what is the object\u2019s approximate speed in miles per hour? (Note: 1 mile = 5280 feet)",
    "choices": [
      "3.4",
      "3.8",
      "34",
      "38",
      "340"
    ],
    "answer": "C",
    "link": "https://gmatclub.com/forum/if-an-object-travels-100-feet-in-2-seconds-what-is-the-103364.html"
  },
  {
    "question": "A car traveling at a certain constant speed takes 2 seconds longer to travel 1 kilometer than it would take to travel 1 kilometer at 75 kilometers per hour. At what speed, in kilometers per hour, is the car traveling?",
    "choices": [
      "71.5",
      "72",
      "72.5",
      "73",
      "73.5"
    ],
    "answer": "B",
    "link": "https://gmatclub.com/forum/a-car-traveling-at-a-certain-constant-speed-takes-2-seconds-126658.html"
  },
  {
    "question": "If 1 kilometer is approximately 0.6 mile, which of the following best approximates the number of kilometers in 2 miles?",
    "choices": [
      "10/3",
      "3",
      "6/5",
      "1/3",
      "3/10"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "link": "https://gmatclub.com/forum/if-1-kilometer-is-approximately-0-6-mile-which-of-the-140731.html"
  },
  {
    "question": "If 100 centimetres = 1 meter, then what is the value of 100 centimetre^2 in meter^2?",
    "choices": [
      "0.001m^2",
      "0.01m^2",
      "0.1m^2",
      "1m^2",
      "10m^2"
    ],
    "answer": "B",
    "link": "https://gmatclub.com/forum/if-100cm-1-meter-then-what-is-the-value-of-100-cm-square-106516.html class=spoiler-link"
  },
  {
    "question": "The speed of light is approximately 1.86*10^5 miles per second. This approximate speed is how many miles per hour?",
    "choices": [
      "1.11* 10^7<br>",
      "6.70 * 10^7<br>",
      "1.11* 10^8<br>",
      "1.86* 10^8<br>",
      "6.70* 10^8"
    ],
    "answer": "E",
    "link": "https://gmatclub.com/forum/the-speed-of-light-is-approximately-1-86-10-5-miles-per-second-this-149492.html"
  },
  {
    "question": "If 10 millimeters equal 1 centimeter, how many square centimeters does 1 square millimeter equal?",
    "choices": [
      "0.01",
      "0.1",
      "1",
      "10",
      "100"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "link": "https://gmatclub.com/forum/if-10-millimeters-equal-1-centimeter-how-many-square-48538.html"
  },
  {
    "question": "According to the formula <span class=MathJax_Preview style=color:inherit><span class=MJXp-math id=MJXp-Span-1><span class=\"MJXp-mi MJXp-italic\" id=MJXp-Span-2>F</span><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-3 style=margin-left:0.333em;margin-right:0.333em>=</span><span class=MJXp-mfrac id=MJXp-Span-4 style=vertical-align:0.25em><span class=\"MJXp-box MJXp-script\"><span class=MJXp-mn id=MJXp-Span-5>9</span></span><span class=MJXp-box style=margin-top:-0.9em><span class=MJXp-denom><span><span class=MJXp-rule style=\"height:1em;border-top:none;border-bottom:1px solid;margin:0.1em 0px\"></span></span><span><span class=\"MJXp-box MJXp-script\"><span class=MJXp-mn id=MJXp-Span-6>5</span></span></span></span></span></span><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-7 style=margin-left:0.267em;margin-right:0.267em>\u2217</span><span class=\"MJXp-mi MJXp-italic\" id=MJXp-Span-8>C</span><span class=MJXp-mo id=MJXp-Span-9 style=margin-left:0.267em;margin-right:0.267em>+</span><span class=MJXp-mn id=MJXp-Span-10>32</span></span></span><span class=\"MathJax MathJax_Processed sf-hidden\" id=MathJax-Element-1-Frame tabindex=0></span>, if the temperature in degrees Farenheit (F) increases by 27, by how much does the temperature in degrees Celsius (C) increase?<br>",
    "choices": [
      "9<br>",
      "15<br>",
      "47<br>",
      "<span class=MathJax_Preview style=color:inherit><span class=MJXp-math id=MJXp-Span-11><span class=MJXp-mn id=MJXp-Span-12>48</span><span class=MJXp-mfrac id=MJXp-Span-13 style=vertical-align:0.25em><span class=\"MJXp-box MJXp-script\"><span class=MJXp-mn id=MJXp-Span-14>3</span></span><span class=MJXp-box style=margin-top:-0.9em><span class=MJXp-denom><span><span class=MJXp-rule style=\"height:1em;border-top:none;border-bottom:1px solid;margin:0.1em 0px\"></span></span><span><span class=\"MJXp-box MJXp-script\"><span class=MJXp-mn id=MJXp-Span-15>5</span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span><span class=\"MathJax MathJax_Processed sf-hidden\" id=MathJax-Element-2-Frame tabindex=0></span><br>",
      "59"
    ],
    "answer": "B",
    "link": "https://gmatclub.com/forum/according-to-the-formula-f-9-5-c-32-if-the-temperature-in-degrees-160658.html"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the speed of X meters per second is equivalent to the speed of Y kilometers per hour, what is Y in terms of X? (1 kilometer=1000 meters)",
    "choices": [
      "5x/18",
      "6x/5",
      "18x/5",
      "60x",
      "3,600,000x"
    ],
    "answer": "C",
    "link": "https://gmatclub.com/forum/if-the-speed-of-x-meters-per-second-is-equivalent-to-the-speed-of-y-ki-127005.html"
  },
  {
    "error": "7_26_23 PM.html",
    "message": "cannot unpack non-iterable NoneType object"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the speed of X meters per second is equivalent to the speed of Y kilometers per hour, what is Y in terms of X? (1 kilometer=1000 meters)",
    "choices": [
      "5x/18",
      "6x/5",
      "18x/5",
      "60x",
      "3,600,000x"
    ],
    "answer": "C",
    "link": "https://gmatclub.com/forum/if-the-speed-of-x-meters-per-second-is-equivalent-to-the-speed-of-y-ki-127005.html"
  },
  {
    "error": "7_26_22 PM.html",
    "message": "cannot unpack non-iterable NoneType object"
  },
  {
    "question": "The distance between two planets is 3.04 \u00d7 10^6 light years. What is the distance between the two planets, in parsecs? (1 parsec = 3.26 light years)",
    "choices": [
      "9.3 \u00d7 10^5",
      "9.9 \u00d7 10^6",
      "9.3 \u00d7 10^7",
      "9.9 \u00d7 10^7",
      "10.1 \u00d7 10^8"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "link": "https://gmatclub.com/forum/the-distance-between-two-planets-is-3-04-10-6-light-years-161745.html"
  },
  {
    "error": "7_26_28 PM.html",
    "message": "cannot unpack non-iterable NoneType object"
  },
  {
    "question": "A rectangular-shaped carpet remnant that measures x feet by y feet is priced at $50. What is the cost of the carpet, in dollars per square yard? (9 square feet = 1 square yard)",
    "choices": [
      "50xy",
      "450xy",
      "xy/9",
      "xy/50",
      "450/(xy)"
    ],
    "answer": "E",
    "link": "https://gmatclub.com/forum/a-rectangular-shaped-carpet-remnant-that-measures-x-feet-by-135045.html"
  },
  {
    "question": "If a rectangular room measures 10 meters by 6 meters by 4 meters, what is the volume of the room in cubic centimeters? (1 meter=100 centimeters)",
    "choices": [
      "24,000",
      "240,000",
      "2,400,000",
      "24,000,000",
      "240,000,000"
    ],
    "answer": "E",
    "link": "https://gmatclub.com/forum/if-a-rectangular-room-measures-10-meters-by-6-meters-by-27351.html"
  },
  {
    "question": "If 100,000 microns = 1 decimeter, and 1,000,000,000 angstroms = 1 decimeter, how many angstroms equal 1 micron?",
    "choices": [
      "0.00001",
      "0.0001",
      "0.001",
      "10,000",
      "100,000"
    ],
    "answer": "D",
    "link": "https://gmatclub.com/forum/if-100-000-microns-1-decimeter-and-1-000-000-000-angstroms-1-deci-195190.html"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the volume of a tank is 4,750 cubic centimeters, what is the volume of the tank in cubic meters? (1 centimeter = 0.01 meter)",
    "choices": [
      "0.00475",
      "0.0475",
      "0.475",
      "4.75",
      "47.5"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "link": "https://gmatclub.com/forum/if-the-volume-of-a-tank-is-4-750-cubic-centimeters-what-is-the-volume-220602.html"
  },
  {
    "question": "If 60 feet of uniform wire weighs 80 pounds, what is the weight of 2 yards of the same wire? (1 yard = 3 feet)",
    "choices": [
      "2 2/3<br>",
      "6 <br>",
      "8 <br>",
      "120 <br>",
      "2400"
    ],
    "answer": "C",
    "link": "https://gmatclub.com/forum/if-60-feet-of-uniform-wire-weighs-80-pounds-what-is-the-weight-of-260458.html"
  },
  {
    "question": "At <span style=font-style:italic>c</span> cents per pound, what is the cost of <span style=font-style:italic>a</span> ounces of salami? (1 pound = 16 ounces)",
    "choices": [
      "c/a",
      "a/c",
      "ac",
      "ac/16",
      "16c/a"
    ],
    "answer": "D",
    "link": "https://gmatclub.com/forum/at-c-cents-per-pound-what-is-the-cost-of-a-ounces-of-salami-260471.html"
  },
  {
    "question": "If 3 miles are equivalent to 4.83 kilometers, then 11.27 kilometers are equivalent to how many miles? ",
    "choices": [
      "2 <br>",
      "5 <br>",
      "7 <br>",
      "6 1/2<br>",
      "7 1/3"
    ],
    "answer": "C",
    "link": "https://gmatclub.com/forum/if-3-miles-are-equivalent-to-4-83-kilometers-then-11-27-kilometers-ar-260472.html"
  },
  {
    "question": "If p pencils cost d dollars, how many pencils can be bought for c cents? ",
    "choices": [
      "100pc/d<br>",
      "pc/(100d)<br>",
      "pd/c<br>",
      "pc/d<br>",
      "cd/p"
    ],
    "answer": "B",
    "link": "https://gmatclub.com/forum/if-p-pencils-cost-d-dollars-how-many-pencils-can-be-bought-for-c-cent-260473.html"
  }
]